paulallen.com 2013-01-15

# Idea Man - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for Vulcan Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, "Vulcan") and applies to the information we collect through www.paulallen.com (the "Site"). By accessing and/or using the Site, you are consenting to the collection, storage, and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Vulcan reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page so you can readily review the most current version. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the bottom of this Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. 

**Your IP Address**  
An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When a user requests a page from the Site, our servers log the user's current IP address. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site. 

**Cookies**  
The Site is developed using Active Server Pages (ASP), and we use per-session "cookies" (pieces of data your browser stores in your computer's memory at Vulcan's request) to establish user sessions on our server. We use the cookies to carry information about usage from page to page through the Site. Vulcan does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. 

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site. 

**Use of Submission Information**  
As stated in our Terms of Use, we do not accept requests for information or funding through the Site. All or any part of the information collected or submitted through the Site (including, without limitation, information regarding funding requests, requests for information or updates, feedback regarding the Site, or any personal information you provide) is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "Submission Information." 

As described in our Terms of Use, Vulcan does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis. Consequently, we are free to use Submission Information for any purpose whatsoever. 

**Disclosures to Third Parties**  
Because Vulcan does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis, from time to time Vulcan may disclose your Submission Information to third parties, including, without limitation, other potential investors, our consultants, our representatives, our affiliated companies and others. 

**Disclosures for Legal Reasons**  
Vulcan will also disclose Submission Information when it believes, in its sole discretion, that the law requires such disclosure or that such disclosure is necessary to: 

  * Comply with the law;
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Vulcan or others; or
  * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public or the users of the Site.

**Links**  
This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Vulcan. Other Web sites (including those that we may link to) may have their own policies. Vulcan has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of such third party Web sites. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [info@vulcan.com](mailto:info@vulcan.com). 

Last Updated: December 13, 2004
